Guide to the Houston Women's Caucus for Art Records
University of Houston Libraries
- Shows, 1981-2003
  - Houston Area
    - Canary Project - Unit Sponsor - The Rose (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Canary Project - Venues, 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Canary Project - "Mother Earth", 1997 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Canary Project - Budget and Donations, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - “Ya Ya Reboot", October 29-December 31, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - “Is this a joke or what?", March 1-31, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - “Above Construction", July 19-August 13, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - “Limp", May 6-June 10, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Email Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - “Sneak PreView", July 7-August 4, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - “Who is Who among Eastern Texas Women Artists", November 1-30, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - "Art in Houston" - Internet, undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979-1997 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Canary Project - Paraphernalia, 1997 (Ovs box 14, Folder 3)
    - Art Celebration, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Arts Task Force, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Canary Project- “Banners Project”, 1997-2000 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Canary Project- “Banners Project”, 1995-1998 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Canary Project - “Banners Project”, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Out of Town
    - 1979-1989 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 1990-1996 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Events, 1982-2001
  The Events series covers all events held by the HWCA that do not fall into the fundraising or the exhibition categories. The years 1982 through 2001 are represented in these folders and are arranged alphabetically by subject, then chronologically within each subject. While many of the artists who showed their work at the Firehouse gallery also gave talks or sat on panels in conjunction with those exhibitions, information about those engagements have been left with the information about the exhibition.
  - Houston International Festival, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Houston Area - Mars Millennium Project, June 21-August 31, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - HoustonArea - “Presentation and Representation", April 15, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Houston Area - Mothers for Clean Air (cancelled event), May 2001 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - HoustonArea - “Picture this” Mystery Mural Project, March 16, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Houston Area - “Working Women Artists and the Legacy of Women’s Art History", March 2000 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - National Women Artists Visibility Event, September 27, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Retreat, September 25-27, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Social, 1982, 1992-1996 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Speaker - AIDS, 1989, 1993, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Speaker - The Artist in Society, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Speaker - The Artist at Work, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 14-15)
  - Speaker - Does Government Funding = Censorship of the Arts?, October 5, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Speaker - Music, Architecture, and the Visual Arts, January 9, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Speaker - “The Many Hats of an Executive Director", November 11, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Speakers - Miscellaneous, 1982-1998 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Studio Tours, 1983, 1990-1995 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Workshops, 1980-2001 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous, 1986-2001 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Christmas With the Webbs, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - School to Work Apprenticeship Program, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - We Won’t Go Back!, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Women Ignite, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Fundraising, 1982-2002
  The Fundraising series covers the years 1982 through 2002, arranged into five sub-series: Contributors, Grants, Events, Reports, and Miscellaneous. The Contributors sub-series includes lists of Gifts-In-Kind, information about the Kroger Share Card, and correspondence with various companies, individuals and organizations in regard to donations to HWCA. The Grants sub-series is arranged alphabetically by organization. The largest of these groups is the Cultural Arts Council of Houston (CACH). This sub-series contains grant applications and correspondence concerning those grants. The Events sub-series is arranged chronologically according to the particular fundraising event. “Drop In, Switch On” is the most recurrent of these events. The Reports sub-series contains an incomplete set of summaries of Caucus fundraising activities. All other fundraising information can be found in the Miscellaneous sub-series.
  - Contributors
    - Gifts-in-Kind, 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Kroger Share Card, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous, 1978-1989 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous, 1990-2000 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Grants
    - Computer Affairs Program, Apple Computer, Inc., 1983 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Greater Houston Women's Foundation, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, November 1, 1980-May 1, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, March 16, 1981-June 30, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, March 1982-July 1982 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, August 1982-May 1983 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, January 1984-October 1984 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, July 1984-July 1985 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, January 1985-July 1985 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, July 1, 1985-June 1990 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, July 1, 1990-June 30, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, May 1, 1991-June 30, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, July 1, 1991-June 30, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, July 1, 1992-June 30, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, July 1, 1995-June 30, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, July 1996-June 1997 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, July 1997-June 1998 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, July 1998-June 1999 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, July 1999-June 2000 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, July 2000-June 2001 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Cultural Arts Council of Houston, July 2001-June 2002 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - National Endowment for the Arts - Interdisciplinary Arts Fellowship Program, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - National Endowment for the Arts - New Forms Regional Initiative Grants Program, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Texas Commission on the Arts, 1982-1990 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Texas Commission on the Arts, 1990-1995 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Texas Commission on the Arts - Artists-in-Education, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Texas Commission on the Arts - Education and Technical Assistance Program, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Texas Commission on the Arts, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Texas Commission on the Arts, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Texas Commission on the Arts, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - TexasCommission on the Arts - Travel Grant, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Various Foundations (denials), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Various, 1980-1983 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Events
    - "An Artful Affair", 1981 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - "Drop In, Switch On", 1994 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - "Drop In, Switch On", 1995 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - "Drop In, Switch On", 1996 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - “Drop In, Switch On", 1996 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - "Drop In, Switch On", 1997 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - “Drop In, Switch On", 1998 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - "4×4 Recreational Vehicle", 1995 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous, 1979-1995 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Reports
    - 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous
    - 1982-1998 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - 1998 (Ovs box 14, Folder 4)
- Members, 1979-1997
  This series includes information concerning the members and membership dues. This series covers the years 1979-1997, and is divided into 4 sub-series: Directory, Dues, Rosters, and Miscellaneous. A complete list of members and their addresses can be found in the Rosters sub-series. Much of the information in the Members series is sensitive, and researchers should contact the archivist before accessing this material.
  - Directory
    - 1979-1994 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - 1992/1994 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - 1998-2002 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Change of Address, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Dues
    - 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - 1984-1987 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 1988-1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - 1995-1997 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Payment Reports, 1989-1992, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Rosters
    - 1979 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - 1984-1988 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - 1990, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - 1993-1997 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Other Chapters, approximately 1980, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Mailing List, 1984, 1990-1996 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Membership Canvas, 1983, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Volunteers, 1995-1996 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Finances, 1980-2001
  The Finances series contains an almost complete financial record of the Caucus from 1980-2001. This series is arranged into four sub-series: Bank Statements;Checks; Receipts; and General. The Bank Statements sub-series ends in 1999; and it is missing June through December 1994, and all but July and September of 1995. Blazek, et al CPA is the accounting firm that handles tax matters for the Caucus. This folder includes predominantly correspondence with that company. The Budgets folder is incomplete, and reflects only the budgets for the activities of the entire Caucus. Budgets for individual exhibitions are found in the folders for those particular shows. The Treasurer folders contain the procedures for the office of the treasurer, and an incomplete set of monthly reports made by the treasurer at Board Meetings. The Yearly Financial Statements folder is not complete, and includes annual and biannual reports.
  - General
    - Blazek, et al. CPA, 1981-1992 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Budget, 1981-1999 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Deposits, 1979-1985 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Deposits, 1986-1995 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Income Tax - Exempt Status, 1977-1983 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Income Tax - State of Texas, 1980-1996 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Income Tax - Returns, 1982-1993 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Ledgers, 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Ledgers, July 1981-October 1982 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Ledgers, 1985-1991 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - River Oaks Bank, 1983-1996 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Treasurer - Procedures, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Treasurer- Reports, 1980, 1984, 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Yearly Financial Statements, 1979-2001 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - 1985-2000 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Bank Statements
    - 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - 1982 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - 1983 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - 1984 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - 1985 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - 1987 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - 1988 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - 1989 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - 1990 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - 1991 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - 1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - 1993 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - January-May 1994 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - July, September 1995, January-July 1996 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Checks
    - Blank, undated, approximately 1990 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Stubs, March 15, 1978-January 6, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Stubs, January 13, 1981-December 7, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Stubs, January 17, 1984-January 15, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Stubs, January 15, 1985-January 13, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Stubs, January 10, 1987-June 28, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Receipts, 1982-1996 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Receipts
    - 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 1982 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - 1983 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - January-May 1984 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - June-December 1984 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - 1985 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - 1986 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - 1987 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - 1988 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - 1989 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - 1990 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - 1991 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - 1992 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - 1993 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - 1994 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - 1995 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - 1996 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Conferences, 1978-2002
  The Conferences series contains fliers, invitations, programs and brochures for conferences attended by the HWCA between 1978 and 2002. There are two sub-series: National Women’s Caucus for Art and Other. The thirty-five folders are arranged chronologically within their sub-series. In 1988, the National Women’s Caucus for Art held their annual conference in Houston. Thus, within the National Women’s Caucus for Art sub-series exists a longer grouping for the Houston conference, arranged by topic.
  - National Women's Caucus for Art
    - Washington, D.C., January 30-February 3, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - New Orleans, LA, January 30-February 2, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - San Francisco, CA, February 24-26, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - New York, NY, February 23-26, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Philadelphia, PA, February 15-18, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Toronto, Ontario, Canada, February 21-24, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Los Angeles, CA, February 12-16, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - New York, NY, February 1986 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Boston, MA, February 10-13, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Houston, TX - Audio Service, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Houston, TX - Bus Service, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Houston, TX - Catering, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Houston, TX - Cocktail Receptions, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Houston, TX - Exhibitions, A-M, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Houston, TX - Exhibitions, N-Z, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Houston, TX - Hotel Arrangements, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Houston, TX - Mayor Whitmire, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Houston, TX - Museums and Galleries, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Houston, TX - Newsletters, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Houston, TX - Panels, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Houston, TX - Planning Procedures, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Houston, TX - Programs and Brochures, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Houston, TX - Progressive Dinner, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Houston, TX - Publicity, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Houston, TX - Registration, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Houston, TX - T-Shirts, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Houston, TX - Volunteers, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - San Francisco, CA, February 13-15, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Chicago, IL, February 11-13, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Seattle, WA, February 1-3, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - New York, NY and Chicago, IL, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - San Antonio, TX, January 24-26, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Boston, MA and Philadelphia, PA, February & June, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Philadelphia, PA, February 7-12, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Los Angeles, CA, February 9-10, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - New York, NY, February 21-25, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Chicago, IL, February 2001 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Philadelphia, PA, February 18-20, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Houston, TX – Administrative Materials, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Houston, TX - Audio, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Houston, TX – Clippings, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Houston, TX – Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Houston, TX – Promotional Materials, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Houston, TX – Speeches, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Other
    - Mid-America College Art Association, October 25-27, 1978, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - "NOW and the Future", May 16-18, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - "Visions: The Women's Expo", June 17-19, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - The Mayor’s Summit on Women, November 19-20, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Miscellaneous, 1980-1994 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Photographs
  The Photographs series is one of the strongest in the HWCA collection. The photographs in this series depict various events and artwork for exhibitions sponsored by the Caucus. Within the sub-series, the items are arranged chronologically according to event or exhibition. Dates in brackets are estimates based on the location of the photograph in the original arrangement. Unknown photographs and undated photographs are at the end of each sub-series. Most people depicted in the photographs are unidentified. Those who are identifiable are labeled on the tissue paper separating the photographs. Each folder indicates the number of items in the folder, and the type of photo - black and white (b/w), or color. Where possible, the artist of a particular work has been identified.
  - Negatives
    - Firehouse (b/w), approximately 1982 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - "Private Rites" (color), January 22-February 23, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - "Out of the Cold" (color), 1995 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - "Aubrey McCaskell's Place" (color), December 18, 1995-February 28, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - "Why Girls Can't Paint Cows" (color), January 6-February 26, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - "Salon des Oeuvres Refuses" (color), May 5-June 2, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - "1/2 of 1/2 of 1/2" - Matuschka (b/w), March1-April 22, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Unknown Show, (b/w), undated (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Catalogue and Exhibit, undated (Ovs box 14, Folder 13)
  - Proofsheets
    - Firehouse Renovation (b/w), approximately 1982 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - "Private Rites" artwork (b/w), January 22-February 23, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - "Self-Images" artwork (b/w), 1985 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - "Self-Images" artwork (color), 1985 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - "Contemporary Women in Documentary Photography" artwork (b/w), March 1-24, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - National WCA Conference - Houston, TX (b/w), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - HWCA Board (b/w), approximately 1995 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - “Mother Earth” ground breaking (b/w), September 1995 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Slides
    - Artwork (color), 1978-1989 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - National WCA Conference New York, NY (color), 1986 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - "Contemporary Women in Documentary Photography" artwork (b/w), March 1-24, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - "Women in Art" installation (color), 1987 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - National WCA Conference Houston, TX artwork (b/w), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Members' Names, 1990, undated (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - “Social Reflections” artwork - Elisa Alvarado (color), July 24-August 7, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Artgirls of the West artwork (color), January 6-February 26, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - "1/2 of 1/2 of 1/2" - Matuschka artwork (b/w), March 1-April 22, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - “Slip and Slide Program” – Sharon Bode Messimer (color), January 13, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Unidentified Event (color), undated (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - “Banners Project”, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Various, 1990-1992 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Prints
    - "Stones" reception - Lucy Lippard (color), February 19, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - National WCA Conference Washington, D.C. (b/w), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - "An Artful Affair" fundraiser (color), September 25, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - "12 On Site" Planning (color), September 1980 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - "12 On Site" Installation - Viveka Barnett (color), October 23, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 81)
    - "12 On Site" Installation - Gertrude Barnstone (color), October 23, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 82)
    - "12 On Site" Installation - Marilyn Biles (color), October 23, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - "12 On Site" Installation - Cecile Burns (color), October 23, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - "12 On Site" Installation - Linda [Gratz?] (color), October 23, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - "12 On Site" Installation - Heidi Stanfield (color), October 23, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - "12 On Site" Installation - Vicki Stewart (color), October 23, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - "12 On Site" Installation - Tracy Trajan (color), October 23, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - "12 On Site" Installation - Martha Terrill (color), October 23, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - "12 On Site" Installation - Toby Topek (color), October 23, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - "12 On Site" Installation - Tralene Vassilopolos (color), October 23, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - National WCA Conference San Francisco, CA (color), 1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Membership Party and Reception (color), December 5, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - "Swamp Songs" - Clyde Connell (b/w), September 20-October 27, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - "Homages in Clay" - Jose Varela (color), December 1984-January 1985 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Member Show Catalog - Opening, (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Member Show Catalog - Viveka Barnett (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Member Show Catalog - Gertrude Barnstone (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Member Show Catalog - Malinda Beeman (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Member Show Catalog - Wayne Blythe (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Member Show Catalog - Peter Brown (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Member Show Catalog - Derek Boshier (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Member Show Catalog - Chuck Dugan (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Member Show Catalog - Bobby Duncan (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Member Show Catalog - David Folkman (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Member Show Catalog - Sally Gall (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Member Show Catalog - Robert Harris (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Member Show Catalog - Ron Hoover (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Member Show Catalog - Benito Huerta (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Member Show Catalog - Terrell James (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Member Show Catalog - Lucas Johnson (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Member Show Catalog - Pam Johnson (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Member Show Catalog - Lynn Knippa (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Member Show Catalog - George Kraus (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Member Show Catalog - Arturo Lindsey (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Member Show Catalog - Bert Long (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Member Show Catalog - Jack Massing (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Member Show Catalog - Peter McClennan (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Member Show Catalog - Jesus Baustista Moroles (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Member Show Catalog - Helen Orman (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Member Show Catalog - Jim Poag (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Member Show Catalog - Pam Pool (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Member Show Catalog - Lynn Randolph (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Member Show Catalog - Charlie Sartwell (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Member Show Catalog - Gail Siptak (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Member Show Catalog - Susan Smith (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Member Show Catalog - Gael Stack (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Member Show Catalog - Earl Staley (b/w), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 46)